大家好！
Hello everyone!
在这个视频里 我真的很想在我的真实电脑上测试新的2989恶意软件
In this video, I really wanted to test the new 2989 malware on my real computer.
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果 已获得翻译授权
使用AI工具翻译，如有不准确的地方请在弹幕或评论区指正，谢谢！
如你所见 我有个叫“恢复”的注册表文件
So as you can see, I've got the reg file called restore.
这基本上是一个注册表文件 包含我恶意软件修改的所有注册表项
And it's basically the reg file with all the registry entries that my malware modifies.
所以你看 这就是这个文件
So as you can see, here's the file.
那我们就直接在真实电脑上运行它吧
Let's go ahead and run it on a real computer.
它会变得多卡？
How laggy is it gonna be?
因为它会弹出无数个窗口
Because it creates a billion windows.
我们来瞧瞧
Let's find out.
目前还不卡
No lag so far.
有意思
Interesting.
这说得通
That makes sense.
通知中心打不开 因为窗口抢占了焦点
The notification center does not open because the windows take focus.
嗯 就是这样
So yeah, there's that.
即将有强光闪烁！
把那个小窗口给我
Give me the naglet.
好耶！
Yes!
这确实比在虚拟机上好太多了
That's genuinely significantly better than on the VM.
太棒了！
That's awesome!
所以 我真的很开心
So, um, I'm really happy.
你可能听得出来
As you can probably hear.
我有点遗憾通知中心被抢占了
I'm kind of sad the notification center gets hogged.
但如果有需要 我大概能修好它
But I can probably fix that if I wanted.
太漂亮了
Gorgeous.
我现在大概能在Word里运行任何东西了
I can probably run anything in Word right now.
我得稍微试一下 因为焦点被抢走了
I have to try a little because the focus is getting hogged.
蓝屏来了
Here comes the blue screen.
出现了
There it is.
在真实硬件上
And on real hardware,
听起来就是这样
that's how it sounds.
还不错
Not bad.
它要重启了
It's gonna restart.
我需要帮它吗？
Do I need to help it?
帮它一下吧
Let's help it.
所以 在真实硬件上这就是2989
So yeah, that's 2989 on a real hardware.
原标题：2989.exe on a real computer! 原作者：Enderman
原视频上传日期：2026年7月18日
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
字幕制作不易，喜欢的话支持一下我吧！
那是MSI Vector 17HX
That was MSI Vector 17HX.
其实不太依赖硬件
It's not really gonna be hardware dependent.
绘制窗口需要一点资源
Needs a little bit of resources to draw the windows.
对 就是这样
Yeah, that's how it is.
感谢观看
Thanks for watching.